welcome to the stola the stoah is a
digital campfire where we go here and
dialogue about what matters most at the
night's edge what's happening now
[Music]
all right
welcome to the dark stoah I see a lot of
familiar faces so most of you know the
drill but for the uninitiated these are
weekly sessions where we look at the
world with our eyes open we negatively
visualize the future and we disabuse
ourselves of our cherished beliefs and
we do this through the wisdom of Pat
Ryan the magician of first principles
the red pill pharmacist he has another
one of his signature mic drop
presentations for us tonight and the
theme is a dark one it's on blackmailing
so buckle up the structure for the
evening is two parts the first part is
Pat's gonna give presentation and the
second part we'll have a chance to have
a dialogue with him and asking questions
so in a moment I'm gonna hand it over to
him and as he gives his presentation pay
very close attention so that you can
come up with some good questions and
then you can start throwing them in the
chat and then we'll ask them right and
now I give you Pat Ryan howdy folks
sounds like you were announcing your
wrestlers oh thank you for another
edition of stoic gentleman ladies
everyone involved thank you very much I
appreciate the live feedback and the
chance to interact with humans I don't
get that very often so thank you very
much this is called blackmail inflation
I will be going into the opposite of
last week's talk last week's Hulk was
morality machines this is about the
machine making us amoral so it's a
somewhat inversion and I will be talking
about some pretty hairy topics and I
will do my best to keep my trademark
humor about and please don't take that
as me being glib or
non sympathetic to victims of this type
of stuff I'm just trying to present a
scenario and which does involve this
stuff so with that said let me share my
screen we'll get started all right whoo
this is a tough one I've had limited
success in explaining this topic to
people because it requires a whole heap
of prerequisite knowledge to really
understand why this is such a big
problem and I've done my best with the
previous episodes to prepare you for
this one in particular there's a couple
more that come after this but this is a
this is a keystone piece of the overall
message I'm trying to convey so we all
know what blackmail is there's a lot
about it that we don't know so I'm I'm
just gonna take you through the journey
and break down any questions so and beep
in computers and don't forget they check
them out at least once all right
so most people think that blackmail is
bad letters it's actually not in the
Scottish and frightening where you have
actually meant written tribute it's
basically all it meant and so you had
like very rowdy Scots hijacking and
raiding English farmers and basically
extorting them with their violence so
you know you can take my life but you
can't take my capacity to extort you
with violence
these poor British farmers they just
just want to farm in peace they're not
upset about this thing it's they're
being forced to hand over their money at
sword point and it's just not a good
practice
for these guys these guys love it
obviously know about a hundred years
later an actual black male was trying to
do the same thing over in South Africa
and they leave the British alone they
just want to wreck the world in peace I
mean come on this is just this level of
course I'm kidding but that's basically
the origin of the word blackmail and
we'll go from there so this is the
origin of the law of blackmail actually
dates back to Roman times surprisingly
and finding this book was quite the
treat it's on JSTOR if you're interested
its information wants to be free but the
law wants it to be harmonious that's
that's a challenging situation to
resolve because in Roman law it wasn't
enough to have dirt on somebody you were
actually required to sleep the dirt to
yourself if you had it on somebody and
you were only allowed to reveal it if
there was a public benefit to do so you
couldn't just walk up to someone and say
I know what you did you better pay me
that was actually illegal you couldn't
do that and that starts with Roman law
that actually jumps over to papal law
and the canonists which then moves over
to English law as well and this book
details that evolution to about a
thousand years so this whole section is
is just reaffirming what I just said
assertion of the truth of the shameful
fact being revealed was not in itself
sufficient to constitute a legal
privilege truth was not wholly
irrelevant if the relative to revelation
was false there had to be a very good
reason for it to be approved for it to
be privileged but even if it was true
the revelation of shameful information
was privileged only if the revelation
had been made with good purpose and
dealt with the matter that is that the
public authorities had an interest in
having revealed again not enough to
simply have dirt on somebody these were
very face oriented people and Chinese
culture if they said in your saving face
is a very important concept it was very
apparently very important in Roman law
as well
and then when it came time for the
candidates who were the when the the
papal Authority was constituting their
laws and how they conduct themselves and
then spreading it through christened
them they would go cite this Roman law
this practice of blackmail being
extortion on this there was a public
interest and they would actually cite
the Virgin Mary as as a purpose from as
a an example of it so they would
basically say if Joseph ran out and said
hey Mary's pregnant by the spiritual
baby that I didn't impregnate well that
was a violation of Jewish law your wife
was pregnant by something else so Stoner
right that was the punishment had he had
done so Christ would not have been born
so they actually cite that as saying
like well Joseph had blackmail on Mary
but didn't act on it so that was their
entire legal argument which is like this
kind of bizarre but that's how they made
sense of this ancient Roman practice of
extortion and this is yeah so this is
beginning to detail how the law imposing
silence this is basically saying this is
setting the tone for when this segment
this section right here is setting the
tone for the evolution of the law from
Roman to the cannabis and then from here
over to English practice so the English
in English law they start doing the same
thing so there's like this kind of semi
tenuous line from blackmail being dealt
with in the legal space coming from
Roman law English law and that's
important because by the time we get to
the American Revolution here we go
that's this is also technically an
extension of British law was the
American Revolution it was one of the
few revolutions conducted entirely by
lawyers that's basically yeah right
so here's an example of this practice
kind of coming into fruition straight
from Roman law Alexander Hamilton was
America's first treasurer and a blue
churches favor accountant because of
Broadway he had a lover on the side
Maria Reynolds as a baroque wife ooh and
you know she came to a with a sad story
my husband left me oh no I do please you
know give me money I need help he's like
hey here's three grand and some D on the
side don't tell my buddy
of course she told everybody so her
husband the notorious Days of Our Lives
actor James Reynolds by law if you had
if you had engaged in another man's life
in sexual matters in early American law
you had to duel the man it was one of
they didn't have to but the the guy had
the right to challenge you to a duel and
he don't want to get shot which is
ironic because he actually does get shot
later on in a duel
I guess not by James Reynolds our
favorite days of our lives actor you
zoom like a shot by him apparently
so he basically says I won't challenge
you to a duel if you pay me he is a con
man hi I don't shooting I guess I'll
take it so he's he's throwing money to
this dude and by the way keep winking my
wife so keep doing it because I need
more money so he's basically a pimp now
I need a pimp at that but no and she's
in on it too
so from the very jump at the highest
levels of American banking we have
always blackmailed our officials from
the jump from the very start of the
American Revolution and this is all pre
dating back to Roman law so why is this
good enough for the Americans let's get
the British involve a lot of the British
doing well here's Queen Victoria
eventual Graham because it's not
incident it's 18 whatever and it takes
you know six months to ship a selfie
across the world so its eventual Graham
it'll get there and she reigned for 63
years from the House of Hanover
saxe-coburg and Gotha
German house
surprisingly people always forget that I
mean looks German if you really want to
get into stereotypes but for 63 years
she ruled and she was the first monarch
to be photographed at length at
extension this is just a snippet of the
collection that's available in Getty
Images but this was done by the
d'oeuvres of type which I can't do
French at all but it was the predecessor
to the camera and that's why you have
this sepia tone a sepia tone kind of
feel that's that's a byproduct of the
technology that's not a filter for you
new kids who don't know better there's
some colorized versions and stuff like
that so you're looking at 20,000 images
like 20,000 images of a reigning monarch
which has never been done before in
human history that's really you gotta
like step back for a second and think
about what that means the ability of a
monarch to teleport her face in front of
you when that has never been a
technological possibility before that
shit would blow your mind if you were a
Dirt Farmer for your entire life
you'd be like oh it's the Queen who's
this thing and a council meeting that's
someone the first who that someone
defers to that someone's defers to okay
it's a queen and now she's in front of
you now there's an image it's looking
like a human and you're like oh whoa
technology right so she learned all of
the routes they she pioneered all of the
propaganda techniques the tricks of
photography how to present yourself and
you see it you see it kind of as like
this evolution of learning how to do it
it's not a particularly beautiful person
by modern standards but she's learning
here right she's learning let's do a
profile face like like Roman coinage
but she never really looked straight at
the camera except for like here and
she's never really looking at the camera
she's always off in the distance
somewhere else looking at something else
something else is more important than
the person looking at her it's almost
like a prestige thing okay so that's the
background that's the psychological
around I'm trying to bring you back to
and that's important as we make the next
steps so Queen of England right queen of
like pride like Golden Age England when
they had the largest capture of landmass
and they were on top of that shit she
was like peak right so one of her long
projects was India big time India stuff
getting the trade in the British Raj
trying to take the cotton trying to take
the opium and investing heavily in
railroads big heavy investments in roads
the English I mean the English and the
Indians India is a huge place to start
us getting rare railroads all over India
is a massive massive undertaking that
Americans don't quite like grasp like
it's as significant as putting railroads
in our country which is very fast to
accept no jungle right we have no jungle
to deal with they have a lot of that but
it's it's a totally different problem so
because of that you have the Indian
population which was massive back then I
think it was close to some ridiculously
huge number by 1860 standards yet
railroads bringing the modern
conveniences of European industrial
product making to India in a very quick
way India was barely able to keep up
then you had some of the hero mythology
about it the British did come in and
they did kick out some Muslim rulers who
were oppressing the new populations of
certain parts of it - that's where that
giant twenty-some-odd kit like 20-pound
diamond comes from which is now part of
the crown jewels there's a lot of legal
dispute about this thing she Cates she
booted all them out so many of the
Indians here kind of like that story and
they celebrated her in addition to this
massive technological revolution of
putting down railroad and bringing
industrialism products into India that's
a lot of change going on in India and at
the top is this monarch and then you
have HSBC which is a bank that basically
converts poppy seeds into Hong Kong
that's basically all they do this is
world's premier drug-running Bank it
would not be possible without in him all
of the opium that India made ran through
this Bank so that they could take the
silver the hold on let me step back
opium wars British were outputting a lot
of goods to China China was ho-hum about
buying British products so basically
British silver was dumping into China
and the silver was never coming back the
British said give us our silver back and
the Chinese said go pound sand
I don't care we don't want your fancy
technology and our medieval playground
go away and the British said fine then
we'll flood your country with opium and
only take silver for the opium so
basically China became a bunch of heroin
addicts as the only way to get silver
from China to India to HSBC back into
the world economy this was so terrifying
opium was so crippling that eventually a
nationalist Empress I believe decided to
fight back when she did she put all our
soldiers in the field the British sent a
single ship up the yangzi not a soldier
could touch it because 90% of them were
opium addicts they couldn't even fight
it wasn't even a possibility so
basically the whole of China surrendered
to a single ship and that's how they got
Hong Kong and they held on to it for
like 100 years
it's all HSBC still so this again this
is a huge geopolitical fulcrum point and
right at the heart of it is its Queen
Victoria one could argue that at this
point that Queen Victoria was the most
successful Hindi Emperor volta of
empress of all time in fact the vast
majority the British Empire was a hindi
empire when you get down to population
it wasn't a Christian Empire not by it
not by these numbers look at this 14% I
mean maybe in the halls of power is
probably courage into a degree but in
terms of whole like things you have to
influence the things you have to take
account for its half the Empire was
Hindi that's pretty wild and then this
is what the the medium British subject
that's what they look like that was a
Indian farmer that was the average
British citizen at this
so this is not a person who is fully
acquainted with the Industrial
Revolution doesn't know yet probably
fuck all about rola steam engines and
and gears and all that type of thing
he's just a farmer I mean using a wooden
yoke like it's like the Iron Age right
so when this person is hit with 20,000
selfies of her of his Empress like what
the whole the whole world's changing
here it's crazy fast drugs are all over
the place these Muslims are out of the
picture now half like the Hindi Empire
it's like the biggest empire in the
world now entirely from the British so
this is this is significant when 20,000
photos of Monarch just starts flooding
every part of your culture it's like a I
mean she has an unstoppable narrative
engine her subjects have no exposure in
her history to that type of media
technology its effectively she's a
literal goddess who can teleport her
face on command and that's why
photography was so damaging that's why
it was so why not damaging so I was so
influential incredibly influential
especially at this time given all these
factors that I'm laying out okay
so here we are she uh she conquered
Instagram she conquered eventual graham
and now she's trying her hand at tinder
which is uh matchmaking we're gonna say
she's getting into some matchmaking
issues now she's already bored of
eventual Graham owner of 20,000
southeast and she starts matchmaking
someone for grandchildren like King
George and Princess Alex and you know
well on the second note if you know your
history you'll know where I'm going next
when these guys were match made and she
interfered and she played her game of
putting all these people together it
wasn't long until these guys started
having economic problems and that
ultimately led directly to World War one
right
so in effect her matchmaking helped
really accelerate this war which was a
devastating war for one of two factors
one twenty percent of Europe's e mail
population was completely decimated and
there was no prior
there was no prior event where they
could even compare it to there wasn't
something like the closest they had was
the Battle of seven nations but this was
a scale of decimation that was just
everybody everybody in every society
called us there was also another
byproduct of this because the camera was
invented and because putting these
people in these situations in these
planes and tanks and fields we need a
lot of propaganda to convince a person
to go into this this flesh grinding
machine and so all of these states the
Germans the Russians and the British
they all had massive investments in film
production for wartime propaganda huge
investments absolutely massive and a
Germany put the most money in compared
to everyone else they they they spent
hand-over-fist money building up I think
was called UFA I think it was called
that was the UH the official film
production state backed production for
for Germany so this by-product happened
so we took these these these
demographics of these derision types and
we just basically jumped the generation
to moving pictures and almost like a
single leap and we did it at scale now
we have all these have all these selfies
right we're all pretty regal nice
they're uh they're historically valuable
they had tremendous influence in
propaganda when it came to India but
were they all perfect you think there's
greater than zero nude selfies of her
somewhere I need have to be a bit of a
conspiracy theorist to think that maybe
someone who has unaccountable power
didn't use this technology for sexual
enjoyment you'd have to be you'd have to
go out on a pretty far limb for me to
believe that kind of thing I'm willing
to believe for the sake of the rest of
this presentation that it's very
feasible that a Empress of the world's
largest Empire probably enjoyed a little
bit of pornography either being in it or
seeing it and I'm pretty sure that
a lot of people who would have loved to
seen it not just for its erotic factor
as much as you can get even taste out of
it but also for the power that the black
male would have I'm not willing to
believe there are absolutely or I can't
believe that there are zero lewd selfies
of this Queen this Queen Victoria we're
talking about right what is their secret
is this her secret was there a lewd
selfie a film an erotic thing
catastrophic blackmail on the Queen
that's an interesting question
that's an interesting company name wait
a second who ran that company Oh is this
guy max wax no you probably never heard
of him this is dude raynelle brands here
and Victoria's Secret is basically a
glorified pimp but who was running his
money he only invested in one person
now most billionaires they have like
these diversification strategies and
he's big trusts and complicated shell
games not Lex
now that Lex knew what he was doing he
only invested in one person just one he
didn't add any advisors he had nothing
he had one person to invest in and that
was every chip Steve that's right the
guy who just doesn't keep he just seems
to keep not killing himself it's the
weirdest thing
oh and who's his best friend oh well
look it's the distant relative of Queen
Victoria wow this is Wow this is
interesting
I'm really starting to think that there
are more than 0 lewd selfies of this
monarch guy just putting that out there
right just an idea it's the alum 90 so
what happens at the end of World War 1
when the Germans have now this surplus
of film production capability there's no
more war and the Germans lost so they do
what Germans do they engineer it even
further and make it better but they lost
the war so they're pretty dehumanized
about that whole experience
unfortunately
losing the war and by losing so many men
and by the shame of the international
pressures that were put upon them to
repay the war not just their tad but
also the tablet of the victors why all
the concepts of dehumanization start
becoming the norm the Dadaist movement
was was heavily heavily influenced as a
byproduct of war Rwanda it was just it
was nonsense it was exploring
dehumanization tones and I don't mean
dehumanization the negative tone I kind
of do but it's it's basically trying to
make sense of where they went wrong and
it turns out that the German way of
doing this is to just surround yourself
with so much wrong
this was accelerated because of the
technological surplus of production from
one they can mass-produce almost
anything you'll see right here it's like
it's a pig head and like you know
military garb and they were cheap labor
for the world because of the
International prohibitions that were
upon them they were extremely cheap and
everybody wanted Germans to produce a
lot of stuff so so they they are
basically slaves of this arrangement
effectively their entire national output
is at the benefit of price price
advantages of other nations and then
their art is reflecting that subservient
state it's almost as if it's kind of
kind of agitating the German population
as well simultaneously is humiliating
little bit of both so what are the
Germans add to film production this
Caligari was a if you've ever seen seven
and if you've ever seen any film where
it reveals that the main character is
insane the entire time seven was
probably a bad example but if you ever
seen that trope
it came from this film this this film
started that whole thing Caligari is one
of these it wasn't that popular when it
came out
[Music]
but a lot of film people who were really
serious about their craft they saw this
it's just like a mind-blowing thing
you'll see if you ever watch this film
you'll see these very these kind of
concepts a very surreal abstract non
connected non natural world that the
characters are interacting with just
disconnected from react or abstraction
as a way maybe escapism from the from
the pressures of this situation of
course everyone's this film metropolis
was is still legendary in any type of
film a film analysis it's Fritz Lang's
work who was an arc architect and you
see that in in the film it's just huge
like everything is huge everything's
like these grand epic buildings and big
open spaces and this is grandiosity of
world and the Germans were exploring
this stuff and again they were because
of the huge amount of surplus film
production the film was also assisting
this this dehumanization exploration
process and if anything I'm I'm very
sure that American audiences are not
familiar with this stuff because when
you win a war you tend not to look at
the enemies as humans and don't take my
word for it this is a good book that
actually explains the transition of
German films how propaganda gets
mastered here and how all the propaganda
we associate with Adolf and Hort ler
actually starts here is where this is
where the whole explanation of a
breakdown the film techniques and
everything else this book does a
fantastic job making that gap if you
don't take my word for it
so the overall takeaway of this slide is
that the Germans lost and their art
showed that they lost and they knew they
lost there is no way out
so what if what if this dehumanization
had another effect as well what if it
allowed a new opportunity okay so the
other thing about the Germans and during
the file our period is that it was can
the Babylon of in fact there's a Netflix
show called Babylon Berlin I highly
recommend it it's pretty good
it's about this period and the
dehumanization wasn't just part of the
arts it was also part of their sexuality
and thus in urban centers at least
Berlin in particular Cologne to a degree
and you'd have international players
from all over the world flying into and
divine Mar Germany they could get a
prostitute for the equivalent of like
five cents that's that's a hell of a
deal it has literally the best deal you
can find on the planet that paid that's
a plane ticket the boat ticket is it's
it's a negligible cost compared to the
volume that you can come in with your
prices so the type of prostitutes were
men women children animals any fetish
you can think of all of these people
were broke they're in a hyperinflation
period so they sold their bodies as if
it was a commodity to again the art is
commodity of the human experience and
commodity of the human itself so every
part gets commodified hmm okay so let's
think about this you have all these rich
powerful people going to Berlin you have
this surplus of foam you have this
surplus of sex workers is it really that
hard to think that the Germans were
capable of blackmailing a bunch of
powerful people who are indulging and
the sexual services of their citizens I
again it's not a hard leap to make I
know the Russians were doing it
the Russians are certainly they
pioneered a lot of the techniques of how
to do that at the there would later
become the KGB but I think the Germans
had a head start makes you really wonder
how did it like home to power what
blackmail did he have apparently he had
all of it it would all go to
industrialists capitalists bankers rich
wealthy Nobles they all went to Berlin
for these prostitutes in every single
type of insane
sexual fetish you can think of not just
the humiliating stuff like oh he's a guy
wearing a dress haha like killing people
and cutting them and beating them to
death
that type of shit too it's not hard to
to make the leap that this was also a
black male concentration centre as well
and just to give an example of what what
I'm going on to Eldorado was a very
popular gay bar and probably LGBT bar
and current parlance and invite more
Germany and that's that's a transgender
person right so miss Eldorado so this is
if if the identity of this person was
revealed there's a good chance that
there's a lot of social shame associated
with that in fact this is you know back
in 2005 New York recovered it there was
an investigator in Germany at the time
who was dealing with these types of
people investigating them and saving
them from blackmail effectively so
people would go into Germany for a fun
time do some experimental stuff probably
try homosexuality out just for kicks and
know someone was filming them 200 you
know now you know
now you're gonna if you're an error of a
king or your heir of a banker you just
landed in a lot of hot water and you
can't get out so this is like my own
suicide you saved them from shame and
death that's what this investigator was
doing so as a result he got in very good
with with the with the LGBT scene I
think I think that's the appropriate way
to describe this thing and so he got
along very because he was doing him a
favor he was one of the few people
actually doing it ironically he was
later kill himself because he was taking
bribes from a millionaire banker accused
of child rape they say statutory rape
that's child rape let's call things what
they are and that's another example of
of blackmail having collateral damages
outside of the people person but the
person being blackmailed
being associated with that was death
family Bob family bombs are still fairly
strong in Germany at that time so if
you're associated if you were
blackmailed than the brought shame to
your family and they had to carry the
burden to so it's really explosive stuff
and it turns out Germany was just
collecting this stuff in
all of almost every industrialist you
can think of underworld that blackmail
went and we might get to that we'll find
out so now that we understand the
product or at least the historical
significance of blackmail and how it got
to move from I know a rumor to pay me
off to be silent to oh by the way now we
could have physical proof of what you've
done this is a brand-new technology I
mean we live in a world where just like
movies and TV are everywhere we take it
for granted but this was rock like
foundation shaking stuff when when this
technology came before and there's also
relative value you I mean if you
blackmail this guy what do you think
you're gonna get probably gonna get a
beat-up car and two and a half
no cans of four loko that's not a lot
right if you blackmail this guy hey get
access to his business maybe it's
private jet business class at least
right
if you blackmail this guy get some
rockets and you get a Twitter account
that just can't be bent it's great
that's worth it it's for me instead of
values what if you blackmail that person
well you get access to the British
Empire and the gold standard which the
British said at that time well that's a
hell of a target the blackmail you just
need one photo I don't need a lot of
photos I'm not asking for a billion
Queen Victoria hear me out
I just want one photo just show me your
leg or something show me an ankle and I
can run with that I can run wild with
that trust me alright so we get it but
she got goons you know she's got a lot
of goons they got a lot of guns I'm just
gonna crank this up a bit so I want all
your gold and I want all your land I'm
gonna need more than an egg look I'm
gonna need you to do some really
repulsive shit so universality of taboo
determines the value of your target in
addition to the target itself well
correction University of taboo
determines what you can extract from
your target you can start real simple
with men wearing dresses memes haha
that's funny
and then you get to the real bad stuff
the real bad stuff it's I can't make
jokes about this shit this is terrifying
stuff this is probably the most
universal taboo I can think of so I'm
going to move on but this this stuff is
how you get this stuff so now let's look
at the absolute value of blackmail
there's benefits and costs one once you
put it here it's transferable it's
before I had to like whisper I had to
move evidence or I had to well no I got
a copy
bro that's right here that's in my hand
I can move it around see black males
around I'm moving it it's contextually
unique so it's unique to that time to
the subject to the objects so it's
almost like Bitcoin in a way where you
like this this coin is minted here and I
had it here it's also renewable meaning
I can just bring it up whenever I want
and it has value is a I'm gonna bring it
up ten years from now so it has value
it's cheap to produce comparatively
speaking if my targets the Queen of
England it's pretty cheap to produce
because the amount of stuff I'm gonna
get from it's pretty significant it's
lightweight don't carry one of those
it's after heavy it's reproducible I can
reproduce these films I can make copies
all day long it has an intrinsic value
because of the contextual uniqueness the
target I'm targeting is high value so
it's intrinsic because it is that person
if I target the Pope if I target a king
a policymaker is intrinsically valuable
because of the social value we've put on
those roles it's self renewing which
means once I got you black now at once
oh you bet I'm gonna make you black man
yourself even more you're gonna do it
every year asshole if you're gonna do it
every year I want fresh copies I don't
want you looking back saying oh that was
just me being wild in my 20s
no we doing this every year buddy every
year cuz I want it fresh I got you once
I got you forever total access to the
victims Network and resources we've
covered that what are the costs is this
even worth it right sounds like too good
to be true right all these you get all
these stuff from just this thing I can
convert this metal circle into the
British Empire are you serious we got to
look at the costs
it's expensive to protect because you
really don't want this it's it's
transferable it's lightweight it's
reproducible you have to protect that
you have got to put that outside of
physical access of every human being
alive and it's really important so it's
really expensive to protect because it's
so lightweight it's expensive to
maintain if this stuff to grades you can
degrade my out of luck you got a problem
so you got to make sure that you have
climate control really got to go all out
to get this going and keep this safe
high-priority witness cleanup man if
somebody sees the stuff outside of turn
sorry pal no you got to go and anyone
you've talked to they got to go to in
anyone who knows you probably has to go
to and then I got to silence people who
don't even killed maybe just small isn't
it not gotta hire lawyers and boy it's
it's it's really pricey once you let
those witnesses who should not have been
involved what about the filming crew I
got to whack them to think it's Missy
and if you can't whack him then you got
a black male now I got a black male more
people to protect the original black
male and now it's expanding so this type
of black male is a self expanding virus
once you've target high-profile
high-value targets with it it's just now
I got to go get your kids now I gotta go
get your driver now I gotta go get you
know all these people your accounting
and everything else and if it's a real
high-value target like say a Queen of
England I got to make sure you're alive
because I need your resources and I
can't replace you and I don't want to
replace you you have built-in intrinsic
value to the people to the resources I
don't want to replace you with me I
don't wanna be queen of England I want
your stuff I don't want the
responsibility so I got to keep you in
that position I got to protect you I got
to put armed guards around you and I got
to look for your psychology to see if
you're upset that you're blackmailed I
got a micromanage you because maybe I'm
blackmailing someone who's just too
fucking stupid it's completely possible
that this person has a low IQ he just
happened to be born in a rich family now
I gotta micromanage him and make sure he
doesn't do dumb shit and now he has a
handler and
that's a lot of work and then if the
victims get smart and there's one
example of victims getting smart and in
Argentina oh my god this guy was smart
the victim realizes that they still have
power they know they're being exploited
and they say hey well you've exploited
me for so much stuff that you depend on
me I got you as much as you got me so
this changes the power dynamic entirely
once you get to this stage takes a while
but once you get there it's it's it's
tough it's tough too it's tough to have
that asymmetrical power with a person
once you start depending on on pilfering
them especially when they have resources
that they can command so it becomes a
very dangerous game especially when
you're playing at the geopolitical level
so what does this maintenance look like
why is it so expensive
how does that a thing well let's treat
it like a pipeline production victim
procurement you have to go find people
to blackmail and then you have to go
find people for them to do damning
things to then there's still crew can't
just have anybody film it I mean you
want you really want to risk that you
you want someone to blackmail the Queen
of England you're gonna put an ad out on
Craigslist and be like hey help me do
this like you can't do that you gotta be
real picky so this is a very picky
process and you got a warehouse to stuff
so now you got your film now you got
your blackmail stuff where you gonna put
it remember you got to keep it away from
people it's lightweight
I got private islands I can go get I got
Fiji I got no I can put there I can put
in abandoned Bunker's god bless the Cold
War as plenty of these all over the
place there's a whole billionaires have
a whole pile of them in New Zealand
celestial bodies put in the space
station put it on the moon
no one's going there I mean you might
laugh but so I put it I know it ain't
gonna wear Antartica again places where
people aren't so wherever people aren't
that's where you want your blackmail to
be it's like the it's like the the
opposite of MasterCard right everywhere
you want to go really you want this
everywhere where
one's going then he got marketing so now
you got the goods now you got the team
and you probably whacked these people
already so now you got the marketing you
guys get some Madam's Madam's uh turns
out it's almost like this class thing
where it's like if you add this like
this male peddling stuff looks perverted
but you wrap it up in a madam and all of
a sudden it's classy to sell this stuff
out the people it's so ridiculous and
these are not for you I've had the
unfortunate run-ins with these people in
the past one that comes to mind the
Heidi Fleiss she was a DC madam I never
ran into her but I was adjacent and
she's a man she was a like psychopath on
crack like the mentality you have to be
to be this person is incredible it's not
for everybody
st. gotta go find customers where you
gonna find these customers from right
you're gonna find them again like
Facebook really hey got Victoria's
Newton's law you know what do you got
anybody gonna do you got to be very
distinct you have to be very careful
careful about finding people who either
want this blackmail done to them or
people who don't know that they're about
to be blackmailed which is what you're
really looking for because you want to
go get you one oh you want the power
right well I want to how about a Saudi
prince that's not a Saudi prince what
did i do there I'm so silly oh and I
want the power of a Saudi prince right
so I got a black male so I gotta have
this whole pipeline set up get this
thing set up and then walk this person
into the trap and who does this obvious
pedophile looking person well that's
that's a it's an air of the DuPont's
right he got busted for child all kinds
of terrible child stuff and he didn't
serve a single day in jail go figure
why because he was part of one of these
operations these operations collect all
kinds of people Sawney Prince is just
like they did in Berlin they're
collecting the wealthy they're
collecting industrialist capitalist
bankers governors the nine the same game
just different different customers right
and a lot more polished
pipeline - all right so you get two
customers they don't know they're about
to be blackmailed you this woman's not
gonna blackmail me she loves me no she
talks nice to me come on give me a break
she can't do that she doesn't she
wouldn't hurt a fly right
doesn't even dawn on him the level of
crazy that you have to go through to
even get this process set up but this
madam she's fierce
she has contract enforcement so she has
cartel contacts and spooks and mercs
traffickers and clean up these guys
don't pay these guys start squealing -
all kinds of stuff he can do well before
I get there so this is the this is the
basics you need to conduct a modern
blackmailing high-value target operation
this is like I should probably be
selling this as like a like a start your
own startup pitch but but like this is
this is a heavy investment you need to
have the right talent you need secrecy
and clandestine stuff all day long to
pull it off so let's say you pull it off
right you get your pipeline going well
congratulations you did it but now you
got competition cuz now there's other
pipelines doing the same stuff it wasn't
just Jeffrey Epstein it was also Nyberg
I'm most people outside of Canada
probably never heard of Nyberg but he
was the Canadian Jeffrey Epstein and
then he have intelligence agencies doing
this stuff too
sanaya that's a crowded field you have
like 20 people trying going after the
same high-value targets trying to put
them in honey pots now you got to
compete how do you compete how do you
have a better product right quality
control you need psychologists and
therapists to deal with the people who
are black male we need college that we
need psychologists and therapists to
deal with the people who were the
victims of the blackmailing meaning
either the children or mostly children
in this case because the world has fun
so fucking far out of control that's all
that's left
he needs you need these guys to start
getting people through the trauma that
they went through you need and if they
don't like psychologists and they want a
more spiritual experience we got that
vertical cover - we'll bring in some
pantheon
and humanist channelers they're gonna
they're gonna get your chakras it's all
lined up after being traumatized and
that doesn't work well we got doctors
and drugs to pump you full of that shit
got that all day long we got that on
lock baby so we don't have to worry
about the children were tormenting and
terrorizing we got that on got that
tight nicely tuned and there's one piece
of stuff that was actually most
revealing these guys were one of the
bigger weaknesses in trying to find
these pipelines of child of pedophile
blackmail stuff these guys don't follow
the same rules as these guys they don't
actually these people engage in like
speech and not material and no logistics
these guys deal in logistics as a result
you can actually monitor odd requests
for drugs and you can monitor odd
requests for equipment to to help
rehabilitate children and so these guys
once you start talking to em you can
reveal entire pipelines and if fuck's
the whole game up there was one woman
who specialized in hip surgery in
Hollywood she was the only hip surgeon
in Hollywood and so what happened was
you these asshole pedophiles they would
abused these children and then they
would call her to fixed the hips but she
was the only one doing it and because of
that she was easy to find and that's how
a lot of these other people got strung
out once you started playing in the
material space then it just left
evidence the pipe line all over the
place then you go to normalization I
mean start blackmailing celebrities and
get them in on it too we a celebrity is
authors personalities cultural agents
people that can say well you know it's
okay to be naughty on the side it's fine
come on down do you see we're doing it
it's cool we can all do it right the
media and journalists reporters because
sometimes you can't whack a person you
just gotta destroy the reputation so
what you're doing is you're increasing
the fidelity and you're increasing the
resolution of your ability to conduct
your blackmailing operation using these
players as well but you've had to expand
these people and the same rules apply if
these people
know that you were doing this then you
have a problem so ideally you want them
not knowing you're doing it but if they
get too close these people always got
too close somehow they always got way
too close on them then you got to either
bring them into operational your Wacom
that's basically it and then eventually
once you start you know you are
blackmailing these guys too so now you
can start legalizing ways to increase
the expan you're not you're never
actually legalizing the taboo you don't
want to do that because that would
invalidate all the blackmail instead
what you want to do is you want to
legalize the pipeline's efficiency the
ability to collect more talent and the
ability to get better quality control
and the ability to do better operations
you don't actually want to legalize you
know the great taboos and obviously
bankers and brokers which are the prime
people you get it anyway so you want to
build this whole infrastructure that
that makes blackmailing the most
efficient thing you can think of now
I've been kind of rattling on about this
stuff as if I'm personally doing this no
I'm not personally doing this but I have
studied this for a long time and there's
a reason I run the site called Colt
state and these like no pipelines are a
big part of that so where do you find
these Psychopaths that starter I mean
look look at the amount of people you
need to run a modern I mean this is a
lot of people where do you even find
these Psychopaths to begin with do we
really have that many psychopaths in our
in our world today well the answer is
well you gotta know where to look it's
cults you can find people who believe
the cult is I mean even Julian Assange
was part of a cult he'll tell you all
about it as soon as he leaves Delmarva
but you find people who are who are just
very suggestible and you can shape their
reality and have them do dehumanizing
things prisons they've already selected
themselves for dehumanization so that's
an obvious one orphanages they haven't
they're already broken to a degree
emotionally unfortunately and so you can
shave and grow them from there refugees
they just like ice I'm sorry
that they've already lost everything
usually to a war a bombing a civil war
ethnic cleansing these people have seen
genocide up front they're already pretty
scarred and they have nothing it's not
hard to give him a gun and say hey go go
shoot these people for me insane asylums
I know America kind of ended a lot of
their insane asylums and plenty of other
countries still have them they have
their use you can you can you don't have
to necessarily rehabilitate a person as
much as simply just pick them out and
say you know stand here I'll hold this
camera nobody's gonna believe you anyway
Marx and spooks someone's got to pay the
bills of these guys right when in doubt
you can always hire them NDA's do apply
to them they do take them seriously so
if you're interested give Blackwater a
call gangs gangs are kind of like Marcus
and spoofs they do their own violence
sorting as well their initiation
practices and the intensity like I don't
mean like the stupid gangs I mean like
legit drug trafficking human trafficking
gangs like the real deal guides you
cannot mess with types man mafia is
every way low Sopranos so you can pick
any one of these sources to find these
Psychopaths who then run your blackmail
Network I don't know if there's I don't
know if there's like a psychopath job
search engine somewhere I'm sure there's
a need for it for some miserable human
being
so no those improvements going on now we
have it's not just you're running this
blackmail Network I mean you are
iterating your processes you want them
to be more effective over time so
technology comes into play now we're
looking at different types of ways we
can make our operations more smooth and
effective I mean do we really need to go
out and like poke rich people when
everyone else has already put hooks in
them maybe I gotta go down a step maybe
I gotta start going for judges maybe you
know small business owners who hasn't
been captured already right so we gotta
move into less competitive space social
media I'm sorry I didn't back up a bit
so this leads to what I'm calling Auto
self-blackmailing meaning
people who blackmail themselves on
purpose all the time forever for their
entire life now you can actually find
precisely the personalities you're
looking for social media we're all doing
it wrong Auto blackmailing ourselves
just I'm doing it right now by having
the speed yay
cellphones consumer devices Alexis out
there snitching hard on everybody I
think gets away with it Internet of
Things is it's just gets worse from here
I mean this the air is going to listen
to you at some point
competitive attention economics
attention economics are bad enough when
you compete them people are just they
don't they fall into the trap and you
keep playing
I need more likes and even reviews and
even more monetization blah blah blah
they keep playing this game and say it
just means more and more
self-blackmailing for their audience for
themselves for everyone they know
psychographics the ability to analyze
people based on the evidence they leave
behind on these on this on the internet
that's allowing you to get into the
psychology of a person and make them
blackmail themselves cancel culture we
all love and know that it's what happens
when you get caught with the blackmail
you will get cancelled it's actually a
lesser punishment compared to the
traditional ways of solving that problem
admittedly but people are aware of what
happens when you auto blackmail yourself
too much you're gonna run into this into
this monster right here and then there's
also the cyber warfare element it's an
open field you know that's an open place
and there's a lot of conflict taking
place like it's not just bits and bytes
and viruses it's also psychological
warfare and imporant information
operations that are going on right in
front of you at all times
so all of these factors attribute
towards Auto self-blackmailing which is
an improvement to the black male
pipelines and I can just tap into this
and you get some benefits
congratulations you're you're you're
you're a clever clever businessperson
okay so I've explained the pipeline and
now I'm going to give you a
demonstration of blackmail as a security
asset meaning once you have blackmail on
these powerful people
is very important to keep them
blackmailed as long as you can so that
not only you control their access to
their power base but also so you can
control their interactions with other
players too so let's say it's an
American election and we elected a clown
not going to passing judgment name any
names I'm just saying we elected a clown
as president Oh and president has this
little button that lets and fire nuclear
weapons well now I have a moral problem
we just put a clown in front of the
nuclear button it's obviously not a
nuclear button it's a chain of command
like 200 people has to go through but
we're just going to call it the nuclear
button I don't want that clown touching
that that would be the last joke and
it's not even that funny of a joke so I
don't know the clown touching that so
what do I do well I don't know
I gotta examine uh he didn't just get
there alone get an influential banker
that's how he became president and he
probably has a scientist some fancy
technology he used to hack the internet
and maybe does influence business person
behind it this guy has a whole team
apparently he's got a culture and
spiritual people seem to follow him is a
general this is some influential stuff
here this guy has a whole team and they
all have the ability to influence his
time and his motives to press that
button
this person's whispering in his ear all
Tibet I have to save Tibet you have to
press the nukes and save Tibet this
person all we need more science if we
nuke these people we can improve science
a billion fold this person's like I just
hate humans new people it's it's all of
these things can influence this clown to
press this button and then we have
problems you don't want you don't want
this this arrow is arrow you don't want
happening right and all these people
it's not just this person's decision may
all of these people can do it all these
people can influence this person how do
we stop this how do you make this
scenario not happen it's easy blackmail
every single one of them every single
one using the pipeline that I just
showed you how to build so got a ball
blackmail there we go and guess what you
may press you pressing that you're not
gonna press that button now oh look
hello there how are you oh he thinks
that you can Oh No he's taking a look at
this he thinks you can you can build a
world order out of this stuff if you
wait hold on if you if you decided okay
I got this governing but I got blackmail
on them I got a trade or mean I got them
to add these guys and hey wait a second
I got blackmail and all these people I
can control when they interact with each
other how they interact with each other
wait a second it's almost like this
world order and it's brand-new and I'm
building it I did it I use it I use
black minutes so so I can take these
powerful bodies and if I get blackmail
or all of them I control not just the
wealth of one nation not just the wealth
of one but how they all interact
together I don't care about their wealth
anymore
now I'm steering them however I see fit
I'm not the one doing it this guy I'm
kid I know that guy is sharing this
stuff I couldn't even tell you it's
doing the stuff Billy who's the person
in control here that's not even the
right question to ask doesn't matter who
is in control the point is this stuff is
very feasible and it's happening right
and then like I mean if this is in play
maybe I am a conspiracy theorist right
maybe I'm maybe I'm nuts and there's no
person who was blackmailed so many
people maybe that person doesn't exist
and no one's blackmailed so many people
I don't know I don't know who that is
I've never seen this person in my life I
couldn't even tell you but I know he
didn't kill himself right so we have a
we have a world order in which these
little rules of film have a say I
couldn't tell you the percentage of how
much say they have but they're
definitely an ingredient in the dinner
for sure so what I just showed you is
Wes Fowler
2.0 let's follow it for the for the
nuclear age the agreement that a
psychopath sub-state will play within
the boundaries of their own interactions
and not just worthlessly slaughter
populations for lulz you do that with
this
and some people don't like this
arrangement some people don't like the
fact that they're blackmailed and some
people will go great lengths to make
sure that they get out of it
so now we have to talk about threats to
this cuz this is what's holding the glue
together so what if someone comes along
with a whole bunch of content and starts
normalizing the taboos I got to put a
stop to that person because it's going
to interrupt what I'm trying to do here
all right all the morality police I just
bring him in yeah whatever
yeah I had these people worried about
something and they'll cancel the
normalization because they want the
taboo because two exists because it's a
taboo it's actually fairly horrifying on
its face they're not exactly wrong here
all right well that didn't work let's um
let's make an entire village of claw of
twin babies I kid you not this exists
it's a candy dough sorry but this is a
village in South America where 123 twins
exist that is a statistical
impossibility by the way that is a
distribution that is not even close to
organic which means somebody was
twinning those people on purpose and
guess who it was it was Joseph the
doctor of death Nazi doctor of death
from World War two he escaped Germany he
went to this little village and he
twinned all of these people using all of
the research that he was able to get
from World War from that from the German
breeding programs research so how do you
cancel this like what first why is this
a problem well it's a problem because if
I can't win people then one person can
be blackmailed while the other one isn't
now I can say well we can get rid of
this blackmail curse and then I can put
this person in there so I can have two
people in the same place doing different
things it interferes with this pretty
significantly I gotta put a stop to that
that's it was the Nazi doctor yeah sort
of Jews at it though feel they'll take
I'll take it on all day that's fine so
to ADL's for right morality please but
for humanism cool all right they sounded
great so let's just if we're already
twinning things it's cloning going on I
got six thousand year to thaw brains so
I'm
pretty inclined to think that cloning is
not that farming that's not too hard to
do and this obviously has implications
for the same reason this has
implications so this has got to go
morality please no cloning allowed own
you really get caught doing it you're
gonna get a free plane ride by the CIA
in fact the the Chinese decided to
imprison their clone guy a couple months
back I don't know if you remember that
he came out and say hey we made a clone
sorry flame right for you that's a house
we countering this a file copying right
I mean what if I just got access to this
and copied it all over the place
that would do something interesting
right cuz then everybody would have the
blackmail on all these people and that's
probably not good for any type of you
know world puppeteering that's going on
well this is my old boss this is Edgar
Bronfman he's the guy behind MPAA
who basically said you can't don't
download mp3s I don't know file
music piracy you might remember that if
you're if you're old enough you wouldn't
download a car I don't know if you
remember that ad that was hilarious and
yes I would download a car I would
download a lot of things so I could I
don't know if I download this stuff this
stuff is just nuclear high but he found
a way to kind of plant that down and
then Apple happened and then all kinds
of psychological ways to kind of make
this less interesting okay so we got a
kind of camp in there and then just
straight-up theft let's just steal them
all okay just grab everything all right
let's let's do a mad dash we're going
for the gold here we're just taking it
all that's a fleet that's a free plane
right for you sorry pal know what feel I
make up surprisingly I can use makeup to
make someone look like someone else
doing some basic film tricks welp we got
facial recognition now so that's not
gonna work
sorry you all of these tricks that I'm
showing are and it's a normalization
this is spoofing the person on the film
spoofing the person on the film
destroying the value of the uniqueness
of the film just straight-up stealing
all of it trying to trick people into
thinking they weren't on the film and
then of course Photoshop it's fake news
anything come at Photoshop speakers
right so all
these things are you are being deployed
to protect the value of this and so far
it's kind of working you know it's not
it's not like a solution you put it in
place and forget about it it takes
maintenance you got a channel you know
money into the second thing but this
stuff is controlling Westphalia 2.0
there's plenty of money to go around
that's not a that's not a hard thing to
allocate funds for but we have a problem
even with all of this it's still not
enough because we have one little piece
of problem that's about the hit us hard
just who's gonna show it to you it's
these four people the bravest heroes the
world has ever not I don't know these
fucking people are these people don't
exist by the way those human beings have
never been born
they do not exist and they were deep
faked into existence now you you're
probably squinting you're trying to find
the pixels like I don't know man I don't
know I think those people do not exist
which means I can take and start
generating humans in film in pictures in
anything to do whatever the hell I want
and it's gonna look this real there's
already videos of deep faking Obama deep
faking Vladimir Putin deep faking Donald
Trump you can go look for those they're
available they're everywhere it's
getting better you might say well I can
know if you get down to it I'm gonna
find the deep fake yeah you probably
could I mean if you get into the the
JPEG algorithm you can see artifacts in
the block encodings that are indicative
of a deep faking that is true but there
are people that when they see this just
like when they saw Queen Victoria's face
they're gonna think yeah that's probably
a person so you get the same effect the
same asymmetrical advantage for a time
no what you need is a time because once
you get that asymmetrical advantage
where you can deep fake anybody into
anything into any situation you are now
in a scenario where we can automatically
create blackmail
on anybody I don't need a film crew I
don't need to clean up messes I don't
need to deal with all these problems the
robots gonna do it for me I press button
I get black now on anyone and that's the
future we're about to walk into no why
is this a problem you think well if
everybody's blackmailed then nobody's
gonna believe anything that's true
that will happen you're gonna have and
have a systemic collapse for sure as
nobody believes any face of human
activity ever again sure that's going to
happen but there's a problem okay
remember our little theoretical model of
how you build a world order that's very
brand spanking new what you do is you
have the blackmail and all these people
right but I just showed you technique
which I can create blackmail on any of
these people
put your fake blackmail on this guy I
just made a whole bunch of black men on
that guy now you might think so what who
cares
probably is a scumbag yeah you scumbag
sure but this is the real blackmail and
this is the fake blackmail no thing
about game theory or to you might start
to say hey now wait a second this guy
can use this stuff to plausibly deny
this one uh-oh guess what just happened
it's plausible deniability he can defect
now he doesn't have to play the game
here he doesn't have to be controlled by
the leash anymore he can use this fake
stuff to defect and now he has a problem
he didn't one of the fact he likes his
position of power he wants it he loves
the fact that he's blackmailed he can't
get enough of it he's guaranteed
prestige he has power he has all the
drugs and hookers he wants he fucking
loves it he doesn't want this Bernie you
know what the smokey don't want none of
this
but the robot side to target him because
Lal why not and he sees the problem too
this person's concerned there might be a
defection he's smart enough to get
there's probably going to be a defection
he doesn't want
maybe this guy does so now he's courting
the robot he said go ahead I went out of
this game this is fucking the crazy
train I'm out and this guy he you know
the passages priest over there just
wants to kill everyone he's like this is
kill them all they're all defectors kill
all right so what you've done is with
this fake blackmail you can unravel any
one of these groups by targeting one
person just one doesn't you need to be
the head honcho it's this dude this dude
any of them doesn't matter do your basic
network craft make your target to fun
rattled the whole game comes crashing
down no amount of black males gonna save
you poor clown he's having a tough time
because now that buttons right there oh
it's right there what are we gonna do
how does the story end
so now let's review our cross benefit
analysis again if we add one more cost
can be duplicated without authorization
what happens to our benefits well they
start to disappear oh boy oh oh no all I
have is a transferable renewable cheap
ruse lightweight reproducible good
that's called a fiat currency has no
value whatsoever now I have inflated the
blackmail just as the Marxists inflated
gold and their late 1800s so this would
unravel the entire West Valley in order
that someone pulled this off this leaves
us at the Qataris scenario guitarist is
where the Titans were imprisoned for
their war against the gods and losing
they didn't die they were just in prison
if they were released hmm I'd be a
problem so here's our run-of-the-mill
unaccountable psychopathic billionaire
living on his own self manicuring moral
universe you've probably heard a lot
about this person
you've heard that he's reckless and he's
out of control and he has too much power
and he's he's just he's evil and he's
mean and most of that's probably true
but he also has blackmail on him and
that's what's holding him in mind
because he's not out there dumping nukes
on everybody the only reason he's not is
because it's black what if I unchain him
what if I free the Titan from the prison
what if I free all the Titans from the
prison what happens well yeah a couple
of new key boys for sure at the very
minimum oh these guys are back they're
rich they have access to all the fun
toys oh the real fun stuff smart dust
smart dust is it's a internet of things
for biology you inhale it and I have
your body now I can modify your DNA I
can cheat that kill yourself I can do
all kinds of stuff with this stuff
Christopher Byrd had a whole segment
dedicated to CRISPR you know my feelings
on that fully automated Colt creation
we're gonna get there I promise we'll
get there these guys can make a eyes
make people believe all kinds of stuff
about them robot armies these guys have
access to all the fun toys of
Destruction and when you unchain them
you have a problem a very big problem
but we know how to unchain them now and
we know that it's coming they also have
access to this VPN that can be concise
so cheap sorry but that's it
that's uh that's blackmail inflation so
you can attack my premise and say that
the world isn't ran by blackmail and
that's fine you can do that and I'm sure
there's a million critiques about that
saying that's not true of the world it
is my personal model my frozen model
okay fine right right I can say that or
you can say that miss fine a black male
has a role and has a place it might not
be as central as I'm proposing but again
this is an example of any model that is
black male dependent
and that is all thank you for listening
and good luck setting up your own
blackmail pipe don't do it it's a bad
investment okay
wow that was heavy
thank you so much for that Pat yeah I'm
gonna I'm gonna start asking Pat some
questions in the meantime prepare yours
and throw them in the chat and maybe we
can get a dialogue going but feel like I
need a second to take it all in I guess
like an immediate question comes to mind
which I kind of know the answer to
should I throw out my Google home it
won't matter just get rid of it it won't
it won't matter the cell phones exist
and when you walk into the office other
people have cell phones your track your
there's no way out all right well
following on from that
where does pornhub fit into all of this
that's going to be the accelerator for
deep fakes for sure there's obviously a
demand for certain people being
pornography porn was the accelerator for
the Internet as well so we know what
that model looks like it's predictable
there's metrics and models for it
another question I guess okay so the
question behind a lot of what I was
thinking about throughout this
presentation is who's the most anti
fragile in the blackmail economy and one
kind of like ingredient to want to throw
into that one is I kept thinking about
how Donald Trump is so post truth and
how nothing really sticks to him so if
you can riff on that question and
whether or not that relates to Trump
there is one source of anti-fertility
if it was possible that the blackmail
was already released in advance and it
happened to be encrypted and the key to
decrypt it hasn't been released yet and
technically in a world full of fake
blackmail that would be the only real
blackmail left turns out someone already
did that and he's in prison in Belmonte
right now and Belmarsh right now his
name is Julian Assange now you're going
to see him very soon you're gonna see
some political events that are going to
make him front and center very soon now
you see what's at stake you're going to
see some pretty wild shit like global
pandemics and who knows what else is
coming next so what happens next I don't
know when the real blackmail is left
whoever owns it
Owens that whole network I guess the
question is who's it gonna be I don't
know
on that note do you have any other
predictions yeah I'll save them for more
more material later on but there is
there is a way to nullify the Tatara
scenario it's complicated so complicated
that I'll probably dedicate a slight to
a talk to it you just need to do what
Westphalia tried to do Westphalia was
about getting these Psychopaths to do
their stupid war games in a way that
didn't devastate the world that's all it
was trying to do and they had relatively
okay success you'd have to do the same
thing here these Psychopaths when
they're Unchained you're gonna have to
give them a chew toy to dedicate all
their energy and ever ever into and then
dump all of that violence in to where it
doesn't hurt the rest of us there's a
game beat tries to do that I'm not sure
they're thinking of this scale quite yet
they had they it's what I composes the
fallback for when game a and game B
fails or if either of them fail I should
say what I propose is that you have
robotic wars you have robot armies
shooting each other you don't have
people killing people you just have
robots shooting the robots once you do
that we can talk about something more
elaborate afterwards but then that
exploration as to my reasoning is done
it's gonna require an episode then I can
kind of see where Astro economics fits
into that all right well we got some
questions building up I'm going to
select one of them our peter lindbergh
has a question about defects Peter you
want unmute yourself it's more of a
statement so Pat I don't know if you
know this this is a true story that
Daniel the MC of today his rap name is
deep Big D the statement yeah so the
question I have a question about the
kind of conspiracy theory term
like anytime you broach a subject like
this even if you talk about it from
first principles people are just gonna
like clump you to conspiracy theory or
wackos whatever can you speak about how
the media is weaponizing that phrase
yeah it's um there there's a long arc of
trying to weaponize that phrase dating
back to Vietnam I think there was a it
was important to paint people who could
see behind the mask and the smoke screen
and kind of shame them to a capacity and
say hey this person is a conspiracy
theorist meaning that they are unhinged
they're not using scientific process
they're not using scientific methodology
they aren't speaking in probabilities or
distributions they are speaking in
absolutes and absolutes are evil okay we
can't can't reward absolutes
we can never war in absolutes that
statement of self defeating obvious
conspiracy theorist is a way to shame
complexity analysis for example when you
unravel large things you never have all
the information I mean that's that's a
absurd level of criteria required to
even talk about something I need to have
all the information about a single thing
before I can see us in one word about it
you got your kidney I couldn't say a
single word about anything about was a
criteria
I enjoy personally exploring all kinds
of stuff I don't necessarily have to
believe this stuff I'm exploring I don't
even have to believe the stuff I'm
saying I just like to explore the wild
diversity of human neurology which is a
pastime for me but if you platform them
more you've been any type of power that
of course that's where you feel the full
brunt of the conspiracy theory theory
label
Marshall would you like to ask your
question sure if deep fakes are our
printing press outside of robotic
nationalism do you see any other
pathways to avoid our modern 30 Years
War there is one way that I don't agree
with but it's very feasible if you can't
put kill switches on the power that
steers the world then you put kill
switches and everybody instead that's
probably on the menu at some point just
so you can keep the West follow probably
a 2.0 running it's the medical tyranny
is a way to do it Chris
hmm pretty good research done by Furcal
about that McKell occult regarding
prisons and how you imprison people
getting back to fundamentals and stuff
like that like CRISPR has a bright
future as a prison system it's probably
the only alternative I can see David s
would you like to ask your question yeah
let me see if I can remember what I
asked oh did we we get to a point where
there's some little authentic meaning
that we just don't care anymore like in
a way there's just at some point it's
like you have people are people we're
all we're all I'm more worried about
this stuff with actual threats you know
with the smart dust and whatever else
things that then you can actually do
harm to me but harm my reputation so
what I mean it's are we getting to that
point even if we do that will only
accelerate everything I'm talking about
in order for blackmail to work there has
to be a taboo if you eliminate all
taboos and you get this scenario all the
same if the black male becomes valueless
and you get all this unfolding so I
guess I guess that's a there's a deeper
question there then is that a good thing
or a bad thing I mean in a way the
transition is horrifying if you survive
it
do you have an a sense of how to how
does make it more survivable more likely
to survive the transition Rachel do you
want to ask your question yeah so the
groups have some just playing games with
each other and like not going out and
racking mass havoc I'm keeping your
lunatics at bay I'm most efficient way
to do it and I'm sorry I I think I
what's your most efficient way to do
that like say that you have a new tax on
sociopaths you want them to stay like
within their their own life what what is
the best way to enforce that the best
way to reinforce that is what I call
auto coats which I will be doing an
entire video - oh no coats are a very
complicated concept and I've had to like
to leave all of these little videos
behind it so I can actually address it
psychologically a sociopath will follow
a reality tunnel just like anyone else
so if you can steer that reality tunnel
without revealing your hand that it's
you're steering it then the sociopath
will find meaning and validate oh no
that's been shaped now unfortunately in
order for a reality tunnel to be real
the sociopath must have influence over
its steering and that's gonna interfere
with your plans of micromanagement so
you have to have a genuine feedback
cycle in order for because if you don't
that's the one thing the sociopath wants
is control if they can't control the
reality tunnel they will break the hell
out of it mmm so that's a compromising
between sociopaths and reality engineers
thank you
this might be a follow on from that
question but mimetic caper would you
like to ask yours yeah sure
if blackmail is a way of structuring an
obligation might there be other
alternative ways to structure structure
obligations that aren't obsolesce by
deep fades if there were there'd be a
very strong incentive to pursue those
you know otherwise to get chaos right
mmm yeah that's a that's a solid
question there's certainly pressures to
find such obligation criteria you can
see Bitcoin as a version of that in
terms of enforcement that's where it all
gets messy getting enforcement is where
it gets tough for example it's one thing
to swear fealty to a king and say I'm
your surfing whatever you say I'll do if
there's real economic incentive to that
ensure that fealty is granted if there's
a lot of pressures around that are too
chaotic and the King goes away Jews keep
that chaos at bay sure of course you
will see a restoration of that type of
organic fealty happening in this space
once it starts on rolling that will
happen you will see a very wide
ecosystem of zero trust solutions I
can't I can't tell you which one will be
the one that works on that where it
starts getting tough it's like it's one
thing to sign a piece of paper and then
hold yourself the penalty if you failed
to lean up if you feel Albany it's
another when you absolutely need total
and absolute obligation there are
specific tasks that humans have to do
and where that's the case so if I'm like
funneling if I'm taking if I'm if I'm in
control of a funnel of fifty billion
dollars and it's all money laundering
for example right and that's mine that's
my phone with fifty billion
I need people who run that funnel I
can't be there all day managing issue so
I got to defer to people and I got trust
them in a zero trust matter because they
can take that 50 billion and funnel it
into their pockets I don't want that
that's corruption that's that's that's
my money asshole right but you can
always run to the cops and say hey this
guy's laundering money so now you got me
by the balls so how do I
for stress on you catastrophic black
males the answer so forcing trust if you
don't have catastrophic blackmail then
you're just hiring mercs all day to
kidnap every base family just to hold
them while they do their job basically
that's the old way of doing it I have I
mean should bring it up each had private
if it's well I don't know it probably if
only to matter to you I'm like you can
enforce trust by having people sneak
things I mean that's essentially what's
happening with the black men right
they're staking the dirt on themselves
um and there's obviously ways to stake
you know resource st. quotes right
there's trust those ways to do that yeah
I mean there's trustless ways to do it
but I have to keep deferring to that
that money-laundering situation where
what I'm doing is illegal but I still
need zero trust so you can't go running
that a cops that's where I have to use
force violence or threats of violence in
order to keep you in line so you don't
screw me over basically hey when you're
dealing with like like threats of
violence it would be part of it I'm
gonna have to stop it there Geist we can
pick up on to the end of the hour I
think enough yeah thanks so much Pat and
thanks for everybody who was here and
for participating and for being exposed
to the truth there will be a
continuation of this series every Friday
for the foreseeable future
Pat do you have any final words before
we close out is this some thought
everyone who's listened but as you can
tell I putting some considerable thought
into this I have my two solutions to
this problem I need more this is a
massive issue even Henry Kissinger
despite popping up wildly in this slide
and he wrote a piece in the Atlantic
saying the end of the Enlightenment this
is what he's talking about the end of
the West Valley in order this is how you
end it so people are thinking about this
stuff game B is obviously trying its
hand into into being a system but we
need an ecosystem of solutions otherwise
these Psychopaths you can't put them in
check and you got it thank you for that
can I ask a question I think that it is
reasonable then to have a very powerful
psychopathic Ally and it seems like fine
finding that is probably maybe perhaps
like I don't know but dark yeah yeah
it's a dark hedge of course that
psychopath can turn on you must notice
so that was a good good inference Cara
all right thanks again everybody just a
reminder this Toa is a gift and if you
would like to give a gift in return you
can do so at the link that I just shared
in the chat and we have a bunch of other
events coming up Peter would you like to
speak to any of them before we close off
I think I'm too drunk for that if you
want to talk about your event tomorrow
sure yeah so uh tomorrow every Saturday
at 6 p.m. Eastern I'm running a session
called the metagame mastermind which is
a group where we prototype the creation
of digital gangs to help people build up
their sovereignty and respond to the
medaka prices so that sounds interesting
to you if the buzzwords there were your
buzzwords and then come check it out all
right
have a great Friday everybody thanks
again Pat see you folks